Bluetooth Hello welcome to Bajaj Allianz
General Insurance Company Ltd.
Today I will tell you the process of insurance of motor [ __ ] principal
policy through CSC.
For this you will have to login to CSC
and go to the CSC portal where
you will get the scan option. For two wheeler
comprehensive first party, two wheeler
comprehensive first party, you need two
documents. First is
financial office and second is previous policy
details. If you have a previous year policy
copy, then
as you enter this, after that the
first option comes policy period. The policy
period is one to three years,
you can select as much as you want. After that the
next option is
registration number. Registration number means
vehicle number. As soon as you enter the vehicle number,
details and options will appear like
make, model, subtype, capacity,
registration number and five numbers.
After that the next option is your
previous policy copy, privacy policy
copy. If it is available with you as
I told earlier, then click on yes on it
and if it is not available then you can
add it. You will tick on yes.  So they will
ask you for this NCV meaning No Claim Bonus from them also, it will be there
in your previous policy copy, you can
detect it according to that, the
next option comes PIN code, now as you
enter this PIN code, your premium will start
showing and your ID will also be there on the left side,
value added value means the value of your vehicle
which is applicable at that time,
after that you have to enter the customer details,
customer details first name, last
mobile number, email ID and your address, it will be
mentioned in your RC copy, so you have to easily
field the details, after that you
have the option of profit for payment,
as soon as you click on the profit for payment button, it takes
you to direct payment
where there is an option of a tree,
you will click on it
and your policy will deduct your payment and
your policy will be generated, leave all the arrangements to
us and get a package policy from Bajaj Allianz,
thank you so much